<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overviews on TAT - TextAndTag Documentation</title>
    <link>https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overviews on TAT - TextAndTag Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/</guid>
      <description>Chapter 1 TAT Overview Discover what is Tat and the core-concepts behind it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Tat, aka Text And Tags, is a communication tool - Human &amp;amp; Robot all together.
Some use cases:
 Viewing Pull Requests, Build And Deployment in one place Alerting &amp;amp; Monitoring Overview Agile view as simple as a whiteboard with post-it Team Communication &amp;amp; Reporting facilities &amp;hellip;  Tat Engine exposes only an HTTP REST API. You can manipulate this API with Tat Command Line Interface, aka tatcli, see https://github.com/ovh/tat/tatcli.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concepts</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/concepts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/concepts/</guid>
      <description>Four Concepts: Topic / Message / Tag / Label  Topic  Contains 0 or n messages Administrator(s) of Topic can create Topic inside it  Message  Consists of text, tags and labels Can not be deleted or modified (by default) Is limited in characters (topic setting) Is always attached to one topic  Tag  Within the message content Can not be added after message creation (by default)  Label  Can be added or removed freely Have a color   Think about messages as plain information pieces, their meaning are contextualized through microservices using those messages and views you plug on their topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps LifeCycle / Feedback Loop</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/lifecycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/lifecycle/</guid>
      <description>Feedback everywhere We want feedback, not only when applications are in production, but everywhere. PullRequest, build, Release, Monitoring, etc&amp;hellip;
Following examples show how we are using Tat through our DevOps lifecycle @ OVH.
First of all, TaT was designed to be a hub of all Continuous Delivery and DevOps communcation. By plugin all the software running in Plug all the software running in your DevOps ecosystem to Tat, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to follow all the things in TaT and improve as well team and machines collaboration]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/architecture/</guid>
      <description>Main components of a Tat Installation are:
 Tat, also called Tat Engine. Your can running as many Engine as you want. You can imagine running many Tat-Engine instances on Mesos/Marathon, Kubernetes or Swarm, or configure yourself behind a reverse proxy. Source: http://github.com/ovh/tat Tatwebui: it&amp;rsquo;s a web application, an easier way to call Tat Engine than curl. This application is component oriented, your can display messages with different Views. See next chapter about Tatwebui for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribute</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/tat/overview/contribute/</guid>
      <description>Contributing You&amp;rsquo;ve developed a new cool feature? Fixed an annoying bug? We&amp;rsquo;d be happy to hear from you! Make sure to read CONTRIBUTING file on repository concerned before.
Code Main Components  Tat Engine Doc - http://github.com/ovh/tat - LICENSE - CONTRIBUTING Tatwebui Doc - http://github.com/ovh/tatwebui - LICENSE - CONTRIBUTING Tatcli Doc - http://github.com/ovh/tat/tatcli - LICENSE - CONTRIBUTING  Views  CDS View Doc - https://github.com/ovh/tatwebui-plugin-cdsview - LICENSE - CONTRIBUTING Dashing View Doc - https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>